Hello, Kawajiri residence.
Huh?
No, you have the wrong number.
Superb work, Hayato.
You've kept that meddlesome Rohan at bay.
I dare say you're a chip
right off the old block.
Like I said, you've got the wrong number.
Goodbye.
I'm proud of you, boy.
Now I have even more reason to
provide for my beautiful family.
But first, the adults need to talk.
Honey Bunch, I'd love a
goodbye kiss before I leave.
What are you doing, Hayato?
That's my expensive china!
Why would you do that?
What's wrong with you?
I never know what's going on
inside that head of yours!
You act like you don't hear
me, and I don't know why!
Where did I go wrong?
You can't see it yet, Mom,
but he's a murderous psycho.
If I tell anyone about him,
the listener will explode and
time will reset to this morning.
It may not happen for a while,
but if we keep letting him
have free reign over our lives,
eventually he'll kill us.
But luckily for me, I now know about someone
else who has special powers like Kira!
Rohan Kishibe!
I have to find a way
to talk to him somehow!
I have to get him to help me or we don't
stand a ghost of a
chance of defeating Kira!
Rohan's already here!
If I approach him directly,
he'll get blown to smithereens.
Then I'll be forced to
relive the same morning.
I've got to tell Rohan the info
without meeting him face to face.
It's time to change fate.
What? What?
My face!
What's going on?
Hang on!
Rohan did this to me when
we met that other morning!
Damn it.
But I've been keeping out
of sight this entire time.
There's no way Rohan could have seen me.
Once the wheels of fate are set in
motion, there's no turning them back.
Hayato.
Breakdown, Breakdown Breakdown, Breakdown
Let the voice of love take you
Let the joy of love give her a
dance on My care and the love of
love give her a dance on Let the
joy of love give her a
dance on
Breakdown!
Come on!
The weather report never
said anything about rain!
I'm sure you would like
to believe you shattered
your mother's favorite
teapot of your own free will.
But you'd be wrong.
You simply experienced a reoccurrence of
the pot breaking from the previous morning.
It's preordained, son.
That's how fate works,
as you're about to learn.
If Rohan transformed you into a book the
morning before, then a book you shall be.
That is what makes Deadly Queen's
Bites the Dust unstoppable.
It reverses time and nullifies
the exposure of my identity.
Which means I'll have the
pleasure of watching Rohan
explode into obsolescence and
still make it to work on time.
No!
I can't let Rohan die!
I have to go save him
before it's too late!
Poor Rohan Kishibe.
Now watch carefully.
The fool has absolutely no idea
why he's about to breathe his last.
But I'm sure he's realized that his life
as a manga artist has come to an end.
Eichi!
No, not Rohan!
Oh God, why?
Hi, Ito.
Your visit with Rohan is
now as if it never happened,
and the morning will go
on as it always would.
Of course, I could undo
Bites the Dust right now,
which means that Rohan's death would
become a permanent temporal point.
But for now, I think
I'll let it do its thing.
I suspect a few of his cohorts
will be dropping by shortly.
When they do you're going to make me a
proud papa by exterminating the lot of them?
You're my own personal landmine!
But chin up
as long as you're a good little
secret weapon bites the dust
won't harm you So relax and
do whatever you schoolboys do
Well daddy's off to the station
no slacking at school now!
This is only happening because
he crossed paths with me!
It's my fault!
He met me and got murdered for it.
What now?
Isn't there anything I can
do to stop this monster?
Pardon me, can I ask you a question?
Would you happen to have the time?
My stupid watch seems
to be out of commission.
Hello in there, anyone home?
Yeah, it's 8.33.
You know, I have this weird
feeling I've seen you before.
Now, where was it?
You wouldn't happen to
know who I am, would you?
No.
Oh well, my mistake.
I hope I didn't weird you out or anything.
But now I know it's 8.33.
Thanks!
Mr. Jotaro!
Looks like it is after 8.30.
How strange.
Rohan sensei knew we were coming.
Where'd he go?
These are Rohan Kishibe's friends!
They plan to meet here!
They must have the same
kind of powers as him!
So I bet they all came here to
question me about Yoshikage Kira!
No, no, no, no, no!
If they figure out I'm Hayato Kawajiri
and start interrogating me about Dad,
it's all over for them!
Sorry about that, kid.
I was looking for my friends and I'm
still kind of groggy from oversleeping.
I know I've seen this kid's face before,
but for the life of me,
I can't remember where.
Hey, look!
It's Josuke and Okuyasu!
What's up, bro?
Yo, Koichi!
Hope your morning's been spiffy, Jotaro!
Th-there are two more of them!
Kira told me that others would
eventually be showing up!
He was talking about them!
...the kid's house without
Rohan helping us out.
Sorry, I nearly forgot I was
still hanging on to this.
I believe this is yours.
Oh, thanks a lot.
You know, it might be the angle.
Oh yeah, I'm sure of it.
I know I've seen that face before.
I don't know from where, but he
looks too familiar to be a stranger.
Koichi, look at the name
on his backpack. Huh?
Hi, it's Okawajiri! What?
Crap, they figured me out!
Hayato Kawajiri, what the
hell are you doing here?
Was all this planned?
Wait, could this have something
to do with Rohan-sensei?
What am I supposed to do now?
If these guys start questioning
me about my dad, it's all over!
The bomb will kill every one of them!
No, please don't ask me any questions!
If you guys end up getting killed,
who's gonna get rid of the murderer?
If I have to dupe them, then so be it.
Whatever it takes, I can't let them die.
I'd like to ask you about this photo.
To be more precise, I want to know the
reason behind your video recording.
Be straight with me.
Why were you... Shoot! Nosebleed!
Oh no!
I don't know why my nose
started bleeding out of nowhere,
but I have to find a doctor, sorry!
Hold it!
You said you got a nosebleed, huh?
Let's see it.
Come on, let me see.
It's bad.
I need a doctor.
Nah, I don't think it's that bad.
See?
It's not even bleeding.
Josuke Higashikata, nice to meet you.
That's Jotaro Kujo.
one of my relatives.
Derp face over there is Okuyasu Nijimura.
And that's Koichi Hirosei,
the nicest guy I know.
You go to Budogaoka Elementary, so
you've got some time before class starts.
We won't take up much of your time.
Now, about this picture.
If it's nothing, we'll just be on our way.
It is something, but I can't
answer any of your questions.
Please don't ask.
You see the man you're filming?
Would he happen to be your dad?
I'm begging you!
Don't say anything else!
Crap.
What have I done?
Now they're going to
ask even more questions.
What do you mean, don't say anything else?
They're not gonna stop.
Just what is it that we shouldn't say?
There's nothing I can do!
Does all of this have to do with your dad?
The bomb's gonna go off!
It's gonna kill them all!
What the hell's going on, huh?
Why can't we say anything else?
Yeah, I mean, we haven't
even asked him anything yet.
Given his reaction,
it seems the mere act of us questioning
the kid is what's sending him into a panic.
That's it.
I have no other choice.
If I die here, they'll
still be able to live.
I'm the bomb, so I have to die.
With me out of the picture,
I know these guys will figure out a
way to defeat that devil and save Mom!
It shouldn't be this difficult.
Let's just ask him about
Kosaku Kawajiri already.
Hold on, Josuke.
Something is up with him.
Hey, what's wrong?
Hey.
No!
I can't do it!
Something's keeping me
from slashing my throat.
Wait, what isn't that Kira's? Yeah. It is.
That's a face I'd never forget.
It's deadly queen.
Actually, you're looking at
deadly Queen's bomb type 3.
Bites the dust to attack me.
Now would be futile.
In fact, the only reason you can see me is
because I've already entered your pupils.
It doesn't matter how
many of you have gathered.
together.
The moment you asked about my true
identity, your fate was sealed.
Oh, Hiato.
I guess you're already awake.
I'm glad you finally decided to answer me,
but there's no need to scream
this early in the morning.
Breakfast is ready.
Come and get it.
I tried, but I couldn't stop him.
He got them too.
It doesn't matter what I do now.
In one hour,
fate will run its course and Rohan and his
friends will be wiped out
the face of the earth.
It's over.
It's all my fault.
I can't even kill myself.
Well, if I died,
he wouldn't be able to use his power,
but Bites the Dust is
programmed to protect me.
He's unstoppable!
Yoshikage Kira is a monster!
Unless he dies or decides to shut off
Bites the Dust at just the right time,
those guys are going to be blown sky high!
He's made sure of it!
He either has to die or shut off bites
the dust at just the right moment
It's crazy I never thought
I'd ever be capable
of something like killing
a person in cold blood
I mean, I'm a puny 11-year-old kid What
could I do against a monster like him?
A monster
That's it?
Eleven years old or not, there's one
thing I can use to take him down for good.
Kira called me his secret weapon earlier.
Well, I've got my own weapon, and it's
slumbering in the shadows of the attic.
I've never prayed before,
but if there's a god out there, I
need you to come through for me.
Please, God, help me find the strength
to kill this homicidal maniac.
So I was right the sun makes this
cat plant spring to life then it
attacks its target by shooting bullets
of compressed air it's incredible it
can generate so much power with such
little light awesome I'll use its
killer instinct to send an air bullet
flying kira's way at point-blank
range.
I have a plan, but when and
how should I execute it?
Mom's here, so I can't do it
inside or nearby.
Oh yeah, my hat!
When I leave, he'll put it on my head!
That'll be my chance.
He'll come up right behind me,
right in the point-blank range.
That's when Then I'll get him!
You're kidding!
Why didn't you say we were on the air?
I'm pretty sure Dad said he
wanted another cup of coffee.
Kawajiri residence?
No, wrong number.
This isn't the Sakurai residence.
Sweetie, I have something special for you.
Come drink.
It's a piping hot cup of fresh coffee.
Oh, what the hell.
It's such a pleasant morning.
I suppose one more cup before I leave
for work wouldn't hurt anything.
Everything is set in stone under
Bite the Dust's power, right?
Once something is broken,
it's destined to break again.
And there's not a damn thing I can do.
You said it yourself.
Oh no!
My favorite China tea set!
Take that, ass!
Alright, Mom, see you later!
I'm off to school now!
There's nothing to worry about.
I'll never let anyone hurt you, Mom.
Trust me.
Where did that come from?
He's always so aloof.
I never know what's going on in his head.
But then, we have mornings like this
one, and I can't help but love him.
Let me, I'll have this
cleaned up in a jiff.
No use crying over spilled coffee.
But I hope it didn't burn
you too badly. It's fine.
Don't worry.
He's still not here.
Where is he?
Why hasn't he shown up yet?
What's going on?
He was already here last time.
What's the hold up?
Come on!
The weather report.
Never said anything about rain.
It's already beginning to rain.
I wonder if I accidentally changed
destiny by leaving the house.
before he did.
No, that's impossible.
If he's gonna try and sneak
up to put the hat on my head,
there's no question
he'll try approaching me?
from behind.
Time is running out!
Lightning struck the Pepsi sign!
I've gotta calm down. I've still got
two minutes.
And I have more than two minutes before
Rohan Kishibe spontaneously explodes.
I just have to believe.
He's hiding in the shadow of the tree!
He's been here all along!
How could I have missed that?
Under any other circumstance,
I'd say this morning was pleasant,
but Hayato wasn't himself.
Why, though?
I'm getting a very strange feeling.
It feels like we've relived this
morning several times now. Maybe three.
No, wait, at least four times. Oh no!
Does he sense that something's not right?
It doesn't matter, there's no time!
I have no other choice but
to blast him from here.
Could he have figured out that I'm gonna
use the cat plan as a
weapon to take him out?
Is that why he's deciding
to keep his distance
no way if he knew he
wouldn't be that close? Okay,
I'm only gonna get one
shot to finish him off So I
have to make it count if I
miss Rohan will explode his
friends will be obliterated
and that murderer will
deactivate bites the dust
making the whole thing permanent
If that happens, he ends up the victor.
It's now or never.
Just take one more step to the left.
Hurry up and step out
from the shadow of that
shitty tree so I can
blow you to kingdom come!
What the hell?
He hit himself even more!
The look in Hayato's eyes this morning
radiated a tenacity I've never seen in him.
It was almost the exact
same look those Lao
Tzu Koichi heroes saying Josuke gave off.
I don't know what it is, but something's
telling me I need to watch his every move.
Then again, as it stands, Hayato's
completely helpless. Shit! I'm screwed!
A few seconds past 8.29, and the bomb
will start ripping Rohan Kishibe apart!
What is this?
The brat is panic-stricken.
He's like a desperate rat toiling
and drowning in a cesspool of filth.
I guess I was imagining his tenacity.
Those are the eyes of defeat.
He came out!
You left home without your hat,
so I thought I'd bring it to you.
If you're listening up
there, thank you, God.
Thanks for working your
magic and making that
murderer leave the safety
of that tree's shadow.
I'm ready to do this!
Now die, Yoshikage Kira!
What the...
I did it!
A clean shot.
He still hasn't shown up yet.
Perhaps he took a different
route to school and I missed him.
Prepare to die, murderer!
What the hell?!
You know as of late...
No way!
My nails have shown unprecedented growth,
which got me thinking about how lately my
life has been devoid of all that is good.
But the contents of this
pocket confirm my feeling
that a guardian angel has
returned to watch over me.
Remember when I broke Mom's special
teacup this morning at breakfast?
The coffee spilled on my
wrist, giving me a nasty burn.
So I took off the watch and placed
it safe and sound in my chest pocket.
And lo and behold, it
was the right choice.
Had I not spilled that fateful
cup of coffee, where would I be?
How's this possible?
Things were supposed
to work out this time!
No, I messed up again!
And in a few seconds,
everything's gonna go to shit!
Get out, get out.